자막제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(club.nate.com/24)
수정 금지 / 자유 배포
피드백은 메일로 보내주세요
영문자막 - www.ydy.com
한글번역 - 현준호(lightinstom@nate.com)
좋아, 이제 조금만 더..
All right, just a few more feet. And...
제군들
여기가 바로 엘제밥의 문이다
here we are, gentlemen, the
gates of elzebob.
말도 안 돼
Good lord.
겁 먹지 마, 우리가 97시간 동안
노력한 이유가 이거라고
Don't panic. This is what the
last 97 hours have been about.
제자리를 지켜, 아제로스의 검을 지키려고
맞은 편에 무장한 고블린들 떼거지야
Stay frosty. There's a
horde of armed goblins
on the other side of that gate
guarding the sword of asaroth.
전사들이여, 칼을 뽑아라
마법사들이여, 지팡이를 들어라
Warriors, unsheathe your weapons.
Magic wielders, raise your wands.
장전 완료
Lock and load.
라지, 문을 부숴
Raj, blow the gates.
문을 부순다
Blowing the gates.
컨트롤, 시프트..
Control, shift...
B!!
b!
젠장, 고블린이 너무 많아
oh, my god, so many goblins!
가만히 서 있지 말고
베고 움직여, 베고 움직이라고!
Don't just stand there, slash
and move, slash and move!
진형을 유지해
Stay in formation!
레너드, 꼬리에 한 녀석 붙었어
Leonard, you got one on your tail.
괜찮아, 내 꼬리는 튼튼해서
내가 쫓아낼 수 있어
That's all right, my tail's
prehensile- - I'll swat him off.
레너드, 내가 잡았어
I got him, leonard.
오늘은 고블린 피로 술잔을 채우겠군
Tonight I spice my
mead with goblin blood.
안돼, 라지, 함정이야!
측면에서 공격받고 있어
Raj, no, it's a trap! They're flanking us!
나 잡혔어
He's got me!
쉘든, 라지가 잡혔대
빨리 수면 주문을 써!
Sheldon, he's got raj.
Use your sleep spell!
쉘든, 쉘든?
Sheldon... sheldon?
아제로스의 검을 잡았다!
I've got the sword of asaroth!
쉘든, 검은 무시하고 라지를 구해줘!
Forget the sword, sheldon, help raj!
쉘든은 없어
There is no more sheldon.
난 소드 마스터다!
I am the sword master!
레너드, 조심해!
Leonard, look out!
제길, 여기서 죽겠어
Damn it, man, we're dying here!
잘있게나, 평민들
Good
- bye, peasants!
저 자식 포탈 탔어
the bastard teleported!
이베이에서 검 팔고 있는데?
He's selling the sword
of asaroth on ebay.
돈 때문에 우릴 배신해? 너 뭐야?
You betrayed us for money? Who are you?
난 나이트엘프 로그야
내 캐릭터 세부설명 안 읽어 본거야?
I'm a rogue night elf. Don't you
people read character descriptions?
잠시만! 누가 즉시구매를 눌렀어
Wait, wait, wait! Somebody
just clicked "buy it now.
이제 내가 소드 마스터다!
" I am the sword master!
♪ Our whole universe was
in a hot, dense state ♪
Our whole universe was
in a hot, dense state
♪ then nearly 14 billion years ♪
♪ go expansion started... wait! ♪
then nearly 14 billion years
go expansion started... wait!
♪ The earth began to cool the
autotrophs began to drool, ♪
The earth began to cool the
autotrophs began to drool,
♪ Neanderthals developed tools, ♪
neanderthals developed tools
♪ we built the wall
we built the pyramids ♪
we built the wall
we built the pyramids
♪ Math, science, history,
unraveling the mystery ♪
math, science, history,
unraveling the mystery
♪ that all started with a big bang bang! ♪
that all started with a big bang bang!
The Big Bang Theory
1x03 The Fuzzy Boots Corollary
THE BIG BANG THEORY
Season 01 Episode 03
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-cflily
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Original Air Date on CBS
Oct. 8, 2007
온 몸이 땀범벅이야
세컨드라이프에서 수영 같이 할 사람 없어?
Ooh, I'm all sweaty. Anybody want to
log on to second life and go swimming?
방금 가상 풀장 만들었거든
I just built a virtual pool.
네 실제 모습이건 아바타건 지금 당장은 보기 싫어
No. I can't look at you
or your avatar right now.
이웃집 사람 들어왔나봐
sounds like your neighbor's home.
잠시만
Excuse me.
의도적으로 가져온 편지들 가지고 가
그래야 말 거는 핑계라도 생기지
Don't forget the mail you
took accidentally on purpose
so you'd have an excuse to talk to her.
아, 맞다, 맞다
Oh, right, right, right, right.
옆집 편지를 훔친단 말이지..
Stealing
snail mail- -
페니, 우편 배달부가 또..
아, 미안해요
Penny, the mailman, did it
again... he... oh, sorry.
안녕하세요, 레너드
이쪽은 더그에요
Um, oh, hi, leonard. This is doug.
더그, 이쪽은 옆집 사는 레너드에요
Doug, this is my neighbor leonard.
안녕하쇼, 친구?
What's up, bro?
뭐 그저 그래요
Not much...
친구
bro.
무슨 일 있어요?
Is everything okay?
저 편지함에 또 있어서요, 여기요
Yeah, no, I just... I got
your mail again. Here.
고마워요, 그 아저씨한테 한 번 말해야겠네요
Thank you. I've got to
talk to that mailman.
그러지 마세요, 별로 좋을 거 같지 않네요
Oh, no, that's probably
not such a good idea.
공무원들에게는 딱딱거리는 경향이 있다고
문서화되어 있거든요
You know, civil servants have a documented
propensity to, you know, snap, so...
알겠어요, 정말 고마워요
okay. Well, thank you again.
뭘요, 그럼 들어가세요
No problem. Bye.
아, 반가웠어요.. 친구
Oh, and bye... bro.
뭘 그리 멍하게 생각해
Penny for your thoughts.
무슨 일인데?
What's the matter?
난 괜찮아
페니도 괜찮고
I'm fine. Penny's fine.
페니랑 키스하는 남자도 진짜 괜찮아
The guy she's kissing is really fine.
키스라니, 어떤 키스?
뺨? 입술? 프렌치?
Kissing, what kind of kissing? Cheeks?
넌 도대체 왜 그러냐?
What is wrong with you?
난 낭만적이잖아
I'm a romantic.
희망이라고 눈꼽만큼도 보이지 않던 네 짝사랑이
무의미한 질투로 변한 거라고 하지 마
Please don't tell me that your hopeless
infatuation is devolving into pointless jealousy.
질투하는 거 아니야
걱정되서 그러지
I'm not jealous. I'm just
a little concerned for her.
같이 있던 그 남자 모습이 마음에 안 들었어
I didn't like the look of
the guy that she was with.
너보다 잘 생겨서?
Because he looks better than you?
응
Yeah.
꿈에서나 나올 법한 모습이었어
He was kind of dreamy.
그래도 이제는 페니랑 데이트하겠다는
가슴 속에 사무치고 뒤틀린 환상의 잔해에서
Well, at least now you can retrieve
the black box from the twisted,
olsmdering wreckage that was
once your fantasy of dating her
블랙박스를 회수해 다시는 괴짜의 산에
추락하지 않도록 분석할 수 있잖아
and analyze the data so that you
don't crash into geek mountain.
난 아니라고 봐
사랑은 단거리가 아니라 마라톤이야
I di. Greesa love is not
a sprint, it's a marathon- -
여자를 네 품에 안을 때에야 끝나는
끊임 없는 추구가 바로 사랑이야
a relentless pursuit that only ends
when she falls into your arms...
호신용 스프레이에 맞으며 끝날 수도 있고
or hits you with the pepper spray.
이제 페니랑은 끝이야
No, I'm done with penny.
이젠 현실적이 되야지
나랑 비슷한 사람이랑 만날거야
I'm going to be more realistic
and go after someone my own speed.
예를 들면 누구?
Like who?
글쎄.. 올리비아 가이거?
I don't know... olivia geiger.
절름발이에 눈 풀린
학교 식당 영양사 말이야?
The dietician at the cafeteria
with the limp and the lazy eye?
- 응..
- 넌 시도도 못 할걸
Yeah.
Oh, I don't think you have a shot there.
레즐리 윙클이 최근에 다리털을
깎기 시작했다는 걸 알아냈지
I have noticed that leslie winkle
recently started shaving her legs.
이제 곧 겨울이니까
Now given that winter is coming,
자신이 성적 능력이 있다는 신호를
보낸다는 건 누구라도 예상할 수 있지
one can only assume she's
signaling sexual availability.
- 글쎄.. 너희는 같은 연구실에 있잖아
- 그래서?
I don't know. You guys
work in the same lab.
So?
그건 함정이라고
내 말 믿어, 내가 알아
There are pitfalls. Trust me, I know.
만약 성희롱 법에 연관이 되면
나 혼자 공부해 놓은 게 많으니까 불러
When it comes to sexual harassment
law, I'm a bit of a self taught expert.
하워드, 내가 만약 레즐리한테
데이트 신청하면 저녁이나 먹는 거지
Look, howard, if I were to ask leslie
winkle out, it would just be for dinner.
연구실로 들어가서
옷 벗고 춤출 건 아니야
I'm not going to walk into the lab, ask
her to strip naked and dance for me.
아, 그럼 괜찮을거야
Oh, then you're probably okay.
안녕, 레즐리
Hello, leslie.
안녕, 레너드
Hi, leonard.
레즐리, 내가 실험 하나를..
Leslie, I would like to
propose an experiment...
- 보안경, 레너드
- 알겠어
- goggles, leonard.
- Right.
레즐리, 내가 실험 하나 제안할게
Leslie, I would like p
toropose an experiment.
잠시만, 컵라면을 데우려면 500kW
산소-요오드 레이저로 얼마나 걸리는지 알아보는 중이야
Hang on.
I'm trying to see how long it takes a 500
- kilowatt oxygen iodine laser
to heat up my cup a' noodles.
나도 해 봤는데, 2초면 돼
야채 스프는 2.6초 걸리고
I've done it. About two
seconds. 2. 6 for minestrone.
어쨌든, 신경화학적인 면과 함께
생물 사회적인 조사를 해볼까 하거든
anyway, I was thinking more of a bio- social
exploration with a neuro- chemical overlay.
잠시만, 나한테 데이트 신청하는거야?
Wait, are you asking me out?
우리의 동료/우정 패러다임을 수정하는데 있어
I was going to characterize it as the modification
of our colleague- slash- friendship paradigm
데이트라는 성분을 더한다는 말이야
with the addition of a date
like component,
물론 용어 따위로 얼버무릴 필요는 없겠지
but we don't need to
quibble over terminology.
정확히 어떤 실험을 했으면 하는거야?
What sort of experiment
would you propose?
이쪽 분야에서는
정형화된 패턴으로 받아들여진 거야
There's a generally accepted
pattern in this area.
내가 널 데리러 와서
레스토랑에 같이 가고
I would pick you up, take
you to a restaurant.
그리고는 영화를 봐
Then we would see a movie,
휴 그랜트나 산드라 블록 같은 배우가
나오는 로맨틱 코메디를 보겠지
probably a romantic comedy featuring the
talents of hugh grant or sandra bullock.
흥미로운데
Interesting.
데이트의 성공과 실패를
판단하는 가장 중요한 기준이
And would you agree that the
primary way we would evaluate
either the success or failure
of the date would be based
작별 키스할 때의
생화학적 반응이라는 것에는 동의하지?
on the biochemical reaction
during the good night kiss?
심박수, 페로몬 등등, 당연하지
Heart rate, pheromones, etc. Yes.
그러면 데이트는 잘 했다고 치고
가장 중요한 변수에 대해서 생각해보는게 어때?
Why don't we just stipulate that the date
goes well and move to the key variable?
그러니까, 지금 키스하라고?
You mean kiss you now?
그래
Yes.
키스의 매개변수를 정의할 수 있어?
Can you define the
parameters of the kiss?
입은 가깝게, 물론 낭만적으로
민트 필요해? / 고마워
Close
- mouthed but romantic. Mint?
Thank you.
셋을 셀까?
shall I count down from three?
아니, 자연스럽게 될거야
No, I think it needs to be spontaneous.
어떤 거 같아?
What do you think?
이건 네가 제안한 실험이잖아
네 결과부터 말해야 맞지
You proposed the experiment. I think
you should present your findings first.
충분히 납득했어
Fair enough.
우선 좋은 점은, 좋은 키스였어
On the plus side, it was a good kiss.
테크닉도 적당했고
쓸데 없는 침 분비도 없었어
Reasonable technique, no
extraneous spittle.
반면에, 흥분되는 건 없어
On the other hand, no arousal.
- 하나도?
- 전혀
- None?
- None.
시간 내줘서 고마워
Well, thank you for your time.
내가 고맙지
Thanyok U.
전혀 없었다고?
None at all?
쉘든, 네가 만약 로봇인데
나는 그 사실을 알지만, 넌 모른다면
Sheldon, if you were a robot, and
I knew and you didn'T... ...
내가 너한테 그걸 말해주면 좋겠어?
would you want me to tell you?
상황에 따라 다르지
That depends.
내가 로봇이라는 걸 알면
When I learn that I'm a robot...
내가 그걸 감당할 수 있을까?
will I be able to handle it?
감당할 수 있을거야
SF의 역사는 네 뜻대로 안 되고 있긴 하지만
Maybe- - although the history of
science fiction is not on your side.
알겠어, 그럼 하나 더 물어볼게
Okay, uh, let me
ask you this- -
내가 로봇이라는 걸 알면
when I learn that I'm a robot,
나도 아시모프의 로봇의 3원칙에 따라야해?
would I be bound by asimov's
three laws of robotics?
지금 당장부터 따라야 할거야
You might be bound by them right now.
그렇겠지
That's true.
인간에게 해를 가하거나
인간이 해를 입도록 방관한 적이 있어?
Have you ever harmed a human being
or through inaction allowed
a human being to come to harm?
당연히 없지
Of course not.
인간이 위험해질 수 있을 때를 제외하고
너 자신에게 해를 입히거나, 해를 입히도록 한 적 있어?
Have you ever harmed yourself or allowed
yourself to be harmed except in cases
where a human being would
have been endangered?
음.. 없어
Well, no.
로봇 냄새가 나는데..
I smell robot.
무슨 일 있어?
Hey, what's going on?
30분 전에 인터넷이 다운됐어
Internet's been down for half an hour.
그리고 쉘든이 로봇일지도 몰라
Also, sheldon may be a robot.
레즐리랑은 어떻게 됐어?
So how'd it go with leslie?
한번 키스해봤는데
지구가 움직이지는 않더라
Oh, we tried kissing, but
the earth didn't move.
그러니까 원래 움직이는 383마일보다
더 움직이지 않았다고
I mean, any more than the 383 miles
that it was going to move anyway.
이런, 저 표정 본 적 있어
Oh, I've seen that look before.
이제 2주동안 내내 풀이 죽어서
지루한 인디 락 밴드 노래나 부르고
This is just going to
be two weeks of moping
and tedious emo songs
나보고 애완동물 가게에 같이 가서
고양이 보자고 하겠지
and calling me to come down
to pet stores to look at cats.
내가 그렇게 할 수 있을지 모르겠어
I don't know if I can take it.
그럼 전원 꺼버려
You could power down.
언제나처럼, 이 왈로위츠님께 해결책이 있지
Well, as usual, wolowitz has the solution.
적당한 여자들이 많은 곳을 알고 있지
I happen to know a place where
there are plenty of eligible women
거기라면 레너드 마음에 드는 여자를 고를 수 있을거야
and leonard could have his pick.
라틴댄스는 힙을 기억하세요
remember the latin hips.
어깨는 움직이면 안되고
스웨이를 주는 거에요
Shoulders stay still, and... we sway.
하나, 둘, 셋
One, two, three... ...
다섯, 여섯, 일곱,
five, six, seven.
티쉬맨 부인이 널 찍은 거 같은데
I think mrs. Tishman's
got her eye on you.
나도 그랬던 적이 있지
너도 이제 즐겨봐
I've been there. You're in for a treat.
♪ She said, you don't know me ♪
She said, "you don't know me"
♪ you don't even care ♪
doyou "n't even care"
♪ oh, yeah... ♪
oh, yeah...
하느님 맙소사
oh, good lord.
♪ She said, you don't know me ♪
She said, "you don't know me"
♪ you don't wear my chains ♪
"you don't wear my chains"
♪ oh, yeah. ♪
이 노래 완전 좋아
oh, yeah. God, that's a good song.
이중 살인을 위한 음악CD를
만드는 거라면 그렇겠지
If you're compiling a mix
cd for a double suicide.
그 발톱긁개기둥은 네가 쓰려는 거겠지
Oh, I hope that scratching
post is for you.
무슨 생각하는 지 알아
네 천식은 이미 고려했어
I know what you're thinking. I've
taken your asthma into account.
샌디에이고에 고양이과 유전학자가 있는데
There's a feline geneticist in san diego
세상에서 제일 귀여운
저자극 고양이를 만들었대
who's developed the cutest
little hypoallergenic calicos.
레너드, 잠시만
Leonard, listen to me...
이름도 생각해놨어
I've been thinking about names.
아인슈타인이랑 뉴튼이랑 털장화 하사관
이 셋 중에서 고르느라 머리 깨질 거 같아
I'm kind of torn between
einstein, newton and sergeant fuzzy boots.
레너드, 너 정말로 인간관계에 대한 욕구가
유전자 변형 고양이로 채워질 거라고 생각하는거야?
Leonard, do you really think
you can satisfy your need
for a relationshh witip
a genetically altered cat?
귀엽고, 조그마해서
껴안을만한 고양이라면 그러겠지
Maybe.
If it's a cute, little, cuddly cat.
제발, 레너드
Oh, come on. Leonard...
페니 때문에 이러는 거 다 알잖아
this is obviously about penny.
상관 없어
It doesn't matter.
그 여자는 나한테 관심 없어, 날 거부했다고
The woman's not interested
in me. The woman rejected me.
그래, 네가 페니랑 같이 잘 확률이라는 게
Okay, look, I think that you have as much of a
chance of having a sexual relationship with penny
모든 블랙홀의 중심을
허블 망원경으로 발견할 확률과
as the hubble telescope does of discovering at
the center of every black hole is a little man
전선 안으로 들어가서 불빛으로
회로 끊어진 곳을 찾을 확률과 같지
with a flashlight searching
for a circuit breaker.
그렇지만 말이야
Nevertheless,
페니는 널 거부한 게 아니라는 걸
너한테 꼭 말해줘야겠어
I do feel obligated to point out
to you that she did not reject you.
네가 데이트 신청을 안 했잖아
You did not ask her out.
네 말이 맞아
You're right.
데이트 신청을 안 했지
가서 데이트 신청 해야겠어
I didn't ask her out.
I should ask her out.
아니, 내 말은 그게 아니야
No, no, now that was not my point.
내 말은 고양이를 사지 말라는 거였어
My point was don't buy a cat.
아니, 그래도 네 말은 맞아
No, but you're right.
옆 집 가서 데이트 신청 해야겠어
I should march over
there and ask her out.
이런, 진짜 고양이 키워야 하잖아
Oh, goody, we're getting a cat.
Uh... no.
- 안녕하세요, 레너드
- 안녕하세요, 페니
Oh, hey, leonard.
Good afternoon, penny. So, hi... hey.
Uh...
저녁에 다른 계획 있나 해서요
I was wondering if you
had plans for dinner.
오늘 저녁 말이에요?
Uh, you mean dinner tonight?
사실 저녁이라는 말에는
원래 중의적인 의미가 있죠
There is an inherent
ambiguity in the word "dinner.
저녁이란 원래 밥 먹는 행위가 아니라
시간을 의미하는 거잖아요
" Technically it refers to the largest
meal of the day whenever it's consumed.
그래서 정확히 하자면
제 말은 저녁 식사말이에요
So to clarify here, by
dinner I mean supper.
- 저녁 식사요?
- 네, 저녁이요
- Supper?
- Or dinner.
6시 반은 어때요?
다른 시간도 괜찮아요
I was thinking 6:30 if you
can go. Or a different time.
6시 반 좋아요
Uh, 6:30's great.
정말요?
Really?
좋아요
Great.
여러분들과 어울리는 거 좋아하거든요
Yeah, I like hanging out with you guys.
여러분이요?
Us guys?
네, 쉘든이랑 하워드랑 라지요
다 오는거죠?
Yeah, you know, sheldon, howard, raj.
Who all's coming?
아마도.. 다 올 거에요
They... might all be there.
아니면 그 부분집합만 올 수도 있어요
Or a subset of them might be there.
수학적으로 모르는 게 너무 많거든요
Algebraically speaking, there
are too many unknowns.
예를 들자면, 쉘든이
점심을 퀴즈노스에서 먹었는데
For example, sheldon
had quiznos for lunch.
어쩔 때는 배가 부른데
가끔은 배가 안 부를 때도 있다고 하더라고요
Sometimes he finds that
filling, other times he doesn'T.
가게 잘못은 아니죠
샌드위치 종류는 많으니까요
It's no fault of quiznos-
- they have a varied menu.
상관 없어요
재밌겠네요
Okay, whatever. It sounds like fun.
좋아요, 우리 몇 시라고 했죠?
Great. Did we say a time?
6시 반이요
6:30.
- 진짜 괜찮죠?
- 괜찮아요
- And that's still good for you?
- It's fine.
- 바꿔도 상관 없어요
- 6시 반 좋아요
- 'Cause it's not carved in stone.
- No, 6:30's great.
끌을 가지고 가야겠네요
I'll get my chisel.
왜요?
Why?
돌에 새겨야..
6시 반에 봐요
To... carve the... I'll see you at 6:30.
나 어때?
How do I look?
좀 더 자세하게 말해줄래?
Could you be more specific?
땀이 좀 났지?
Can you tell I'm perspiring a little?
아니
No.
팔 아래쪽에 있는 어두운 초승달 무늬가
완벽히 가려주고 있어
The dark crescent shaped patterns
under your arms conceal it nicely.
몇 시에 만나기로 했는데?
What time is your date?
6시 반
6:30.
다행이네, 지금부터 2시간 15분 남았으니까
Perfect. That gives you
two hours and 15 minutes for
향수의 분자 구름의 농도를 낮출 시간은 충분하겠어
that dense molecular cloud
of aramis to dissipate.
이건 좀 심하지?
Is it too much?
럭비 선수라면 괜찮겠지
Not if you're a rugby team.
By the way, if it should ever
come up, you didn't join us
그런데 말이야, 무슨 일이 생겨도
넌 같이 저녁 먹으러 가면 안 돼
By the way, if it should ever
come up, you didn't join us
넌 퀴즈노스에서
치킨 까르보나라를 먹었으니까
because you stuffed yourself with
a chicken carbonara sub at quiznos.
내가 왜 끼겠어?
Why would I join you?
그냥 그럴 수도 있지 뭐..
No reason.
있잖아, 데이트 하는 건 안 좋은 생각 같아
Oh, you know what, maybe
this isn't such a good idea.
술과 덜떨어진 판단력으로 인해서
낭만적인 저녁을 보낼 가능성은 언제나 존재해
Oh, no, well, now there's always the
possibility that alcohol and poor judgment
on her part might lead to
a nice romantic evening.
술이랑 덜떨어진 판단력이란 말이지
잘 될 수도 있어
You're right. Alcohol, poor
judgment- - it could go well.
물론 다른 가능성도 있어
Of course there is
the other possibility,
이번 데이트로 인해서 6개월동안
복도에서 어색하게 마주치다가
that this date kicks off a
rather unpleasant six months
of the two of you passing
awkwardly in the hall,
둘 중 한 명은 결국 참지 못하고
다른 동네로 이사갈 수도 있겠지
until one of you breaks down
and moves to another zip code.
잘 될 수도 있다고 할 때
그만둘 수도 있었잖아
You could've stopped
at "it could go well.
할 수 있었으면 그만뒀겠지
" If I could've, I would've.
난 정말 좋은 남자잖아
I mean, I'm a perfectly nice guy.
식당에 가서 좋은 저녁식사를 못 할 이유가 없잖아
There's no reason we couldn't go to
the restaurant, and have a lovely dinner,
그 뒤에는 산책을 하고
우리 둘의 공통점에 대해 이야기하겠지
maybe take a walk afterwards, talk
about things we have in common.
'도자기 좋아한다고요?
저도 좋아해요!'
You love pottery? I love pottery!
그러다 잠시 멈추게 되고
일이 어떻게 돌아가는 지 둘 다 알겠지
There's a pause, we both
know what's happening.
내가 살짝 몸을 기울이고, 키스하는거야
I lean in, we kiss.
처음에는 살짝 망설이다가
페니도 나한테 키스할거야
It's a little tentative at first, but
then I realize she's kissing me back.
내 아랫입술을 물었어!
날 원하고 있다고!
She's biting my lower lip! She wants me!
끝까지 가는거야!
드디어 하는거라고!
This thing is going the
distance! We're going to have sex!
이런, 말도 안 돼
Oh, god, oh, my god!
지금 시작한거야?
Is the sex starting now?
지금 공황 발작이야
I'm having a panic attack.
아, 그렇구나, 그럼..
Oh, okay. Uh, well then... calm down.
진정해
내가 진정할 수 있으면 발작을 하겠어
그러니까 발작이라고 말하지
If I could calm down, I wobe having a panic
att... that's why they call it a panic attack.
알겠어, 어서 앉아
All right, all right.
Uh, s- s- sit down.
- 그래, 앉아서 눈을 감아봐
- 왜?
Yeah, sit down. Now close your eyes.
- Why?
- Just do it.
- 그냥 따라해
- 알겠어
Okay.
이제 알파선의 활동을 증가시켜봐
Now try to increase
your alpha wave activity.
- 뭐?
- 생체 자기 제어 방법이라는 거야
What? !
It's a biofeedback technique.
뇌파를 조정해서 긴장을 완화하는거지
It's relaxation through
brain wave manipulation.
전미 신경과학학회 저널에서 읽은 적이 있어
I read a paper about it in
journal of american neuroscience.
근거는 좀 약했지만
기본적으로는 성립할 거 같아
It was a little sparsely sourced, but
I think the basic science is valid.
어디 내가 갈무리해뒀는데..
I probably have it here somewher E.
나 지금 뭐하는거야
이런 일도 못 견디는데
Who am I kidding? I can't
go through with this.
페니한테 전화해서 약속 취소해줘
You need to call her and cancel.
- 내가?
- 응
- Me?
- Yes.
- 뭐라고 말해?
- 나도 몰라
- What should I tell her?
- I don't know.
- 아프다고 해
- 알았어
- Tell her I'm sick.
- Okay.
여기 와서 어디 아픈지 볼 수 있을만한
그런 병으로는 하지 마
Not the kind of illness that will make
her want to come over and take care of me,
그래도 너무 심해서 나중에라도 내가
데이트 신청했을 때 불편해할만한 것도 안돼
but nothing so critical that she'll feel
uncomfortable going out with me in the future
if I want to try this again.
알겠어
Got it.
성병 말고는 없겠네?
So I'm assuming nothing venereal?
결장 정기 검사를 했는데
아직 회복이 덜 됐다고 할게
I'll just tell her that you had a routine
conoloscopy and haven't quite bounced back.
됐어, 전화나 줘
Give me the phone.
취소한다며
I thought you wanted to cancel.
안돼, 내가 안 나타나면
너라도 올 거라고 생각할거야
I can't, because if I don't show
up she'll still be expecting you.
내가 거기 왜 가?
Why would she be expecting me?
질문은 그만 해
난 가서 샤워나 한 번 더 할래
Stop asking me all these questions.
I need to take another shower.
다른 사람들은 여기서 만나는 거에요?
So are the rest of the
guys meeting us here?
아.. 아뇨
Oh, yeah... no.
라지랑 하워드는 할 일이 있대요
그리고 쉘든은
It turns out that raj and
howard had to work, and sheldon...
결장 검사를 했는데
아직 회복이 덜 되어서요
had a colonoscopy and he
hasn't quite bounced back yet.
저희 삼촌도 얼마 전에 검사를 받았어요
Oh, my uncle just had a colonoscopy.
설마요, 그럼 우리한테도 공통점이 생겼네요
You're kidding. Then that's
something we have in common.
어떻게요?
How?
가까이 지내는 사람들 중에서
We both have people in our lives who...
장에 생긴 폴립을 제거하려는 사람이 있잖아요
want to nip intestinal
polyps in the bud.
요즘 물리에서 새로운 건 뭐에요?
so what's new in the world of physics?
없어요
Nothing.
진짜로 없어요?
Really? Nothing?
초끈이론만 빼고요
1930년대 이후로는 별 거 없어요
Well, with the exception of string theory,
not much has happened since the 1930s.
그리고 아직 초끈이론은 증명도 못해요
And you can't prove string theory.
기껏 할 수 있는 건
"내 생각은 논리적으로는 일관성이 있어" 정도죠
At best you can say, "hey, look,
my idea has an internal
logical consistency.
그렇군요..
" Ah.
언젠가는 알게 되겠죠
Well, I'm sure things will pick up.
치즈케이크 팩토리에는 새로운 거 없어요?
What's new at the cheesecake factory?
별로 없어요
Oh, uh, not much.
초콜렛 키라임이 요새 잘나가긴 해요
We do have a chocolate key
lime that's moving pretty well.
아, 그렇군요
Good. Good.
전에 복도에서 본 친구는 어떻게 지내요?
What about your, uh...
hallway friend?
더그요? 글쎄요..
Doug? Oh, yeah, I don't know.
재밌고 착한 사람이긴 하지만
I mean, you know, he's
nice and funny, but...
마실 것 먼저 준비해드릴까요?
can I get you started with some drinks?
됐어요!
No!
- 하지만 뭐요?
- 뭐 좀 마시고 싶은데요
- You were saying? But...
- I'd like a drink.
하지만 뒷이야기 해줘요
그 뒤에 바로 부르면 되니까요
Just say the "but" thing about
doug and then I'll get her back.
알겠어요
그게, 아무래도 제 문제인 거 같아요
Okay, well, I don't know, it's just me.
아직 커트도 다 잊지 못했는데
I'm still getting over
this breakup with kurt
더그랑은 단지 반발심에서 한 거였어요
and this thing with doug
would stju be rebound sex.
그런 이야기는 저한테 하지도 마세요
Oh, don't get me started on rebound sex.
그냥, 제 습관이에요
It's just... it's my pattern.
누구랑 헤어지면
괜찮은 남자를 만나죠
I break up, then I find some cute guy,
그리고는 아무 의미 없이 36시간동안..
and then it's just 36
meaningless hours of...
아시잖아요..
you know.
제가 아는지 모르겠네요
I'm not sure that I do.
한번에 36시간이라는 건가요
is that one 36-hour experience,
아니면 음, 멋진 여름동안
다 합쳐서 36시간인지요
or is that 36 hours
spread out over, say...
one glorious summer?
보통 주말동안이에요
No, it's usually over a weekend,
그러고나면 기분도 별로 좋지 못해요, 진짜로요
and trust me, you do
not feel good after it.
쓸려서죠?
Well, chafing, right?
감정적으로 말이에요
Emotionally.
당연히 감정적으로 쓸리는 거 말이죠
Of course, yeah, emotional chafing.
재밌는 거 보여줄까요?
Hey, do you want to see something cool?
이 올리브를 안 건드리고
이 잔 안에 넣을 수 있어요
I can make this olive go into
this glass without touching it.
- 어떻게요?
- 그게 물리죠
- How?
- Physics.
와, 원심력이네요
Wow, centrifugal force.
실은 구심력이에요
Actually, it's centripetal force,
유리잔이 이 올리브에 가하는 힘은
안쪽으로 생기는거죠
which is an inward force generated
by the glass acting on the olive...
잠시만요
Excuse me.
만약에 올리브에 타고 있다고 생각해봐요
If you were riding on the olive,
그러면 비관성계에 있게 되니까..
you'd be in a non
- inertial reference frame and would...
괜찮아요?
are you okay?
네, 괜찮아요
Yeah, I'm okay.
혹시 케찹 흘렸어요?
Did you spill ketchup?
- 아뇨
- 그럼 안 괜찮아요
- No.
- I'm not okay.
응급실에 안 가도 정말 괜찮겠어요?
Are you sure you don't want
to go to the emergency room?
괜찮아요
이제 피는 멎었잖아요
No, no, I'm okay. It stopped bleeding.
그건 그렇지만 토했잖아요
뇌진탕 걸리면 그런거 아니에요?
I know, but you did throw up.
Isn't that a sign of a concussion?
그렇긴 하지만, 차멀미도 있으니까요
Yes. But I get car sick, too, so...
알겠어요
okay.
차는 정말 미안해요
Sorry about your car, by the way.
괜찮아요
거의 다 창밖으로 뱉었잖아요
Oh, no, it's fine. You got
most of it out the window.
오토바이 탄 그 사람만 안됐죠
The poor guy on the bike.
오늘 재밌었어요
Well, I had a nice time.
저도 재밌었어요
Yeah, me, too.
그럼, 들어가세요
Well, um, good night.
안녕히 계세요
Good night.
- 레너드
- 네?
- Leonard?
- Ahye?
혹시 오늘이 데이트였나요?
Was this supposed to be a date?
오늘 저녁이요?
This?
아니에요
No.
당연히 아니죠
No, of course not.
다들 함께 놀기로 한 거였는데
This was just you and me
hanging out with a bunch of guys
다들 일이랑 결장 검사 때문에
안 나타난 거 뿐이에요
who didn't show up 'cause
of work and a colonoscopy.
그냥 한 번 물어본거에요
Okay, I was just checking.
제가 데이트를 할 때는 말이죠,
데이트 진짜로 하거든요
When I take a girl on
a date- - and I do- -
상대방은 데이트하고 있다는 걸 알아요
she knows she's been dated.
대문자로 시작해서
Capital D.
굵은 글씨체에, 밑줄까지 쫙
boldface. Undeinrled.
데이트하고 있단 말이죠
Da... ted.
아무래도 약한 뇌진탕인가봐요
가서 누워야겠어요, 잘 자요
I think I might have a little
concussion. I'm gonna go lie down.
Good night.
데이트는 어땠어?
So, how was your date?
완전 최고였어!
Awesome!
술과 덜 떨어진 판단력의 승리군
Score one for liquor and poor judgment.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents sync:YTET-cflily
자막제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(club.nate.com/24)
수정 금지 / 자유 배포
피드백은 메일로 보내주세요